<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Monkey See, Monkey Do, Monkey Review</description>
    <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://reviewmonkey.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:13:20 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:13:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Into the Spiderverse</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wow, what can I say other than this movie is a pure treat to watch. As a long time Spiderman fan, someone who grew up in the 1970’s watching the original Spiderman cartoon, watching the terrible live action Spiderman movies that were on TV, and all of the various later renditions with Toby and others, you would think I would have been first in line for this animated movie?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I almost didn’t go. Don’t get me wrong, he is still one of my favorite superheros, but after all of the earlier renditions, a person starts to wonder if the latest movie will actually bring something to the table or if it will just be another cookie cutter repeat. At $9+ bucks a ticket these days, that is a valid question to ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I knew I would have some free time today, and I knew my son wanted to go see it (17) and figured he would go want to go with his friends as boys that age tend to want to do, but he was up for going to see it with his old man, so we went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Spoilers Will be Revealed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just want to put that out there, I’m not going to talk about the plot, give you a run down minute by minute. I went into this movie knowing it was animated and that there was going to be Nicholas Cage in it and that there was going to be more that one Spiderman. That was about it, and I have to say I am glad I didn’t know more, not because it would have ruined the movie, but I like coming into a movie fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;amazing-visual-style&quot;&gt;Amazing Visual Style&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an animated feature film, I could tell from the opening credits and score that this movie was going to be different. The visual styles were fresh, explosive even, the audio assails you in a good way, and the way they characters were rendered gave you the feeling of a comic book but also a more traditional anime movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This continues throughout the movie and made this feel like something completely new. Even the various villains and supporting characters take on new twists and subtle changes in a way that makes them feel completely new and exciting. The experience that I expected to be mildly entertained had me on my seat during many parts of the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;great-story&quot;&gt;Great Story&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As amazing as the visuals and sound were, a movie with a poor excuse of a story will not stand the test of time. Granted this is a superhero movie and isn’t ever going to be a Casablanca or Gone With the Wind, I am going to going to say that it is the best Spiderman movie to date, with Spiderman: Homecoming a close second. And while a lot of movies are as good at home as they are in the theater, I definitely recommend that you go see this in the theater where you can get the full audio and visual impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nicholas-cage&quot;&gt;Nicholas Cage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last thing I am going to say, Nicholas Cage did a fantastic job. He often gets a bad wrap for his acting (sometimes for good reason), but I’ve been a fan since Raising Arizona and I thought he did a great job voice acting in this movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all I have for now, thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/movie/spiderman/marvel/sony/2018/12/15/Into_the_SpiderVerse.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/movie/spiderman/marvel/sony/2018/12/15/Into_the_SpiderVerse.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>spiderman</category>
        
        <category>marvel</category>
        
        <category>sony</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Otterbox Commuter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/half-banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otterbox has long been known for their battle hardened cases that iPhone and Android users have flocked to over the years to protect and cradle the special child that will take up some much of their time and attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They make cases that are designed to protect the baby phone if it is dropped, encase it in a protective sleeve, and in the case of the Defender line a protective plastic face. They are for all practical purposes armor for your phone and I can attest that my son’s Defender case kept his iPhone safe through the harsh junior high years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this review isn’t about the Defender case, it is about it’s little brother – The Commuter series case. I would describe the commuter case as a case for the slightly paranoid user who occasionally drops his or her phone. It takes the features found in the Defender series and shaves them down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me explain.  With the Defender case the user puts the phone into a plastic shell that has a plastic cover and snaps it together. Think Vader getting his helmet. A rubber sleeve is then put around the case. With the Commuter series case this gets reversed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a thick rubber sleeve that goes around the back and sides of phone leaving the front glass exposed. A hard plastic shell that grips the phone on the top, bottom and sides with some convenient cutouts to reduce the hard plastic surface area and expose some of the underlying rubber. The result is a much less boxy case that minimally adds to the bulk.  The attached runner ports keep the lightning port and the headphone jack (how quaint, a headphone jack) covered until needed.  The sound off and on switch oddly does not have a port cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-i-came-to-the-case&quot;&gt;How I Came to the Case&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first bought my iPhone 6 Plus I decided to go the Apple Leather Case route. I was older, more refined, careful.  It seemed perfect. And for a long time it was. I had maybe a single minor drop of a foot with no issue, and generally babied the hell out of the phone, but I would put it in my front pocket. And over time the flex the phone received from sitting down, getting in the car, etc. was enough to cause one of the internal boards to start having a short, and my touchscreen would flicker and stop working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By some stroke of luck Apple care actually replaced the phone for a new one, but the sleek leather case wasn’t going to cut it.  I needed this phone to last years.  But I didn’t want to go for the full Defender case. Here was a sleek phone, did I really want to encase it in a block? As I mentioned I have done it in the past, but this time I decided to make a compromise and went for the Otterbox Commuter series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;overall-impression&quot;&gt;Overall Impression&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t say that there is anything I dislike about this case. The hard outer shell that snaps around the rubber sleeve does a good job of protecting the phone from drops. I have dropped my phone with this case easily twenty or thirty times from various heights. The phone is still working without fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only casualty as can be seen in the picture is the lower corner on one side that took the hit it was intended to do and broke. I can only guess that it was one of the harder falls and maybe hit something just right. The loss of plastic hasn’t hindered the case, but it’s an area that now has slightly less protection, so I’ll have to just hope the rubber does the trick in that area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had this case for more than four years now and it has held up remarkably well. These phones cost so much these days, its only natural to want to put the most protection around the phone that you can, nobody wants to see $800-$1000 just go poof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Otterbox commuter satisfies that need in my opinion.  It has given me peace of mind while still letting me enjoy the slim nature of the phone. Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/iphone/case/2018/12/13/otterbox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/iphone/case/2018/12/13/otterbox.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>case</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surface Book</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Microsoft Surface Book was released to the world on October 26, 2015 according to Wikipedia. It featured a two-in-one tablet design that people who liked the Surface tabled line but wanted a traditional laptop could get behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I purchased my Surface Book sometime in 2016 at the suggestion of a friend who was in love with his. There was a lot to like about it, it was sleek, felt well made, had a funky bendy hinge that people on the net were either loving or hating, and once a special came up on the Microsoft store, I decided to take the plunge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now there are tons of reviews out there that tech fetish spew out the specs, I am not going to do that. Let’s face it, this is an older laptop and this review is really meant for the people looking for a laptop on the cheap. So I will be focusing on what I like and don’t like about this laptop after living with it for 2+ years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;general-impressions--internet-woes&quot;&gt;General Impressions / Internet Woes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned earlier, the build quality on this laptop is really pretty fantastic. Every edge has a finished feel, there is no flex or pieces that are pulling apart even after 2 years. The hinge which at the time I bought it was being depicted as something of a joke hasn’t shown any signs of failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large number of people at the time made it out to be wobbly, and if you were to having it on your lap and type it would slightly jiggle. I’ve used this a number of times on my lap and that has never been an issue. If it was I didn’t notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I recall there were also some people that were running into issues with heat from the base of the units that included the build in GPU (which I bought) causing damage to the screen near the vents. This is something that I &lt;strong&gt;could&lt;/strong&gt; see happening if one were to play a GPU intensive game for long periods, it does get pretty warm and I can imagine people sitting in a Starbucks doing just that, closing it up and putting it into a backpack where the screen would have a nice chance to bake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never decided to test that theory, at times when I was playing GPU intensive games I would always just shut it down and leave it open, letting it cool down before closing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gaming&quot;&gt;Gaming&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me just say that gaming on this Surface Book with the weak sauce GPU it has (I do not have the performance based) is sub-par at best. I’ve played some Borderlands on it, some Elder Scrolls Online, even a bit of Fortnite and it has just been ok (with significant toning down of effects). In a pinch it works, but if you can stick to less intensive games you will be better off.  But really, &lt;strong&gt;seriously&lt;/strong&gt; if playing games is a primary focus for you, do not buy this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;linux&quot;&gt;Linux&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been dual booting this Surface Book pretty much since I bought it. I am using Ubuntu Mate at the moment but most distros should work just fine provided that you get the Jakeday kernel. It doesn’t support the GPU and the built in cameras are not working yet, but touch seems to work fairly well.  His repo is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jakeday/linux-surface&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-annoys-me&quot;&gt;What Annoys Me&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to say that the HDPI 3000x2000 screen turned out to be something I have not been the biggest fan of. What I didn’t realize, or maybe I just convinced myself that it wouldn’t be an issue, is that many applications do not play nicely with HDPI screens. Applications will open with tiny interfaces, or the interface will scale incorrectly, or the menus will be all bonkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using a Linux distro that supports HDPI is key, and for the most part it does a better job than Windows but just marginally. Some apps are fine and maybe its just applications I am playing with where the developer didn’t stop to build in support for HDPI that are the issue. On the Windows side the occasional application runs into the same issue. The Windows application override for scaling can sometimes do the trick, but more often than not it just makes things absolutely tiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running at a lower resolution is an option, but the Surface Book really looks its best in its native 3000x2000 resolution. In both Windows and Linux I have had to either put it in HDPI mode to have the system scale the UI or in Windows increase the text scaling. This is likely because I am old, young whipper snappers might be just fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For games the oddball resolutions that this supports for the game to be in the proper aspect ratio are often not supported by the game and one needs to add them into config files, etc.  This is something else to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving My Face Close to the Screen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way too often I find myself taking my glasses off and putting my nose 3-5 inches away from the screen. This always happens when my wife is in close proximity so she can say “That can’t be good for your eyes”. And I agree, there is just something about this HDPI screen that my eyes don’t like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can safely say that my next laptop will not have a HDPI screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-drives-me-insane&quot;&gt;What Drives Me Insane&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, here is the part of the review you should really take note and pay attention to because this issue drives me bonkers.  Much has been said about how much the touchpad is like the holy grail touchpad found on Apple laptops, and as a touchpad, I have no complaints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what this touchpad does that the Apple touchpads does not do it decide to go rogue and move your cursor around the screen when you type. I can’t tell you how many times I have been typing on the built in keyboard in Word or another application only to find my cursor jumping up or down or over to another position while I am typing and royally messing things up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only solution I have found for this is to either a) use an external keyboard (lol it just skipped around as I was writing this using the built in keyboard - Arrggh!) which isn’t a bad idea when you are at the home office, but the point is to be mobile.  Or b) when using Windows, there is an option to disable the touchpad when an external mouse is plugged in, using a Bluetooth mouse, no luck, you need a wired mouse, which is janky as hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has had a number of updated for the Surface Book to fix a number of major issues but this issue continues to persist which makes me think that there is no solution for it an it is likely a physical issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tablet-mode&quot;&gt;Tablet Mode&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly I have not found myself using it in tablet mode. It gives you a full page landscape or portrait viewing experience which is pretty nice. And the way that the tablet detaches from the base will delight Star Trek fans who got giddy whenever the Enterprise would detach the saucer section, but the batter life isn’t as good as what a dedicated Surface or Ipad would give. You can always turn it around and use it with the base in tablet mode but it is a bit bulky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both of these are not deal killers to me, and maybe I just need to spend more time using it as a tablet to see if it makes me forget about the touchpad and keyboard. But probably not, that really fucking annoys me when it jumps around).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it, this monkey’s honest review of the original Surface Book.  I am going to give it three bananas because of the annoyance the keyboard and trackpad gives me on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/laptop/tech/tablet/2018/12/12/surfacebook.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/laptop/tech/tablet/2018/12/12/surfacebook.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>laptop</category>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>tablet</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Braun Tassimo</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/half-banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I was skeptical about reviewing the Braun Tassimo Hot Beverage Station. I have used pod machines before and the results were always bad. I wanted to keep an open mind, even though the coffee I was about to drink, started out as concentrate in a plastic tub. However as a side note, I would rather drink coffee from a pod than coffee that started out in an animal’s colon (See below - Kopi Luwak). But that’s just me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, the instructions that came with it were in French and I wasn’t able to find any online, although I didn’t really need them. My 8 year old was able to figure out how the pod fit into the machine, and from there, it’s just a press of a button. The first cup of coffee was pretty nasty, as was the espresso, and latte. I think that if the user was not a coffee connoisseur, it may suffice, but I roast my own beans, so this stuff didn’t cut it. It was on par with, oh say, gas station coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My son, however did like the hot chocolate, so maybe they have something with a very expensive hot chocolate machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as other points about the machine, it is a cool looking machine, and makes a fast cup of coffee. It also seems like a low maintenance machine, although it does take up more counter space than the typical coffee machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I would not recommend this machine for anyone who is a true lover of coffee. The different drinks (latte, espresso) are equally bad. It’s kind of a cool looking machine, but overall, not pleased with the product. If you’re looking for speed and caffeine, this might work, but a definite no-go in my book.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/28/Braun-Tassimo.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/28/Braun-Tassimo.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Taking it to the Extreme - Kopi Luwak</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To what lengths would a person go in the pursuit of some of the rarest coffee in the world? Would you climb a mountain, trudge through a rain forest, or shall we say… eat roasted coffee beans that have been Biologically preprocessed by a small Indonesian mammal?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right about now, you are thinking option one and two don’t seem so unreasonable. But if you guessed option three, you would be talking about the rare and exotic Kopi Luwak coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Kopi Luwak, also known as the Asian Palm Civet (Paradoxus hermaphroditus) will selectively choose and consume coffee cherries as part of its diet. During its magical journey, the coffee cherry flesh is removed through digestion and the coffee beans are collected for processing (If that isn’t a Dirty Job candidate, I don’t know what is!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Holy Crap!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At approximately $400 per pound, it had better be divine in nature. Its high cost is due to its unique processing, and limited supply (Approximately 300 kilograms produced each year). For those interested in trying a pot or two, 2 oz. packets are available for between $25-$35.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Damn! That Crap is Good! “&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All jokes aside (its impossible NOT to make jokes), the digestive process leaches out some of the proteins from the coffee beans which are normally responsible for its bitterness. The end result being sweeter, smoother coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keeping that in mind, I was very excited to receive a sample of Robusta and Arabica Kopi Luwak coffee from Troy Davis / Animal Coffee.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me try to describe the smell of Luwak coffee beans — they have an earthy sweetness to them that is unlike any other coffee I have smelled to date. You can tell right away that these beans are different from anything that you have tried before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Neither the Arabica or Robusta Luwak coffee is bitter, those claims are quite true. The Arabica Luwak coffee had a creamy and sweet, almost ethereal taste with each sip. Cream and sugar is not needed with either of these coffees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Buying coffee like this really does need to be commemorated… What better way to do that than with a piece of unprocessed Kopi Luwak coffee! Both natural and lucite encased samples are available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kopi Luwak coffee is an extreme gourmet coffee experience that I think every coffee aficionado should experience at least once in his/her lifetime. I would like to thank Animal Coffee for giving me the opportunity to review this truly unique and rare gourmet coffee. It has been a positive and unique experience that I will not soon forget.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/25/Taking-it-to-the-Extreme-Kopi-Luwak.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/25/Taking-it-to-the-Extreme-Kopi-Luwak.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Illy Medium Roast Espresso Coffee</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As an American unschooled in the world of European coffee, I only recently learned about the Illy coffee company. Intrigued by the name, I decided to see what they were all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 1933 (Trieste, Italy), Illy offers an espresso blend hand picked from nine different growing regions around the world. Illy sells medium or dark roasts, regular or decaffeinated, ground medium, fine or in whole bean form. They also sell their various of the coffee pod which they call — E.S.E. (Easy Serving Espresso) which I did not test.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For my review I obtained three cans of Illy coffee:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Medium Roast, Fine Grind Espresso (Regular)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Medium Roast, Fine Grind Espresso (Decaffeinated)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Medium Roast, Espresso Beans (Whole)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the things I really like about Illy is the way they package their coffee. It comes in a metal can with a screw on metal cap. Unscrewing the top reveals a pop top with a warning that contents are under pressure. As you slowly pull up the tab the seal is broken and there is a hiss of air followed by the most amazingly fresh smell of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;assets/images/illy_cup.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Illy Cup&quot; class=&quot;pull-right&quot; /&gt;Coffee should be kept in a sealed, cool (not the refrigerator!), dry, and dark environment to retain its freshness for the longest possible period of time. The cans that Illy uses are perfect for this, the lids screw on tightly limiting the exposure to air. As an added bonus they can stack on top of each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was curious to see what kind of espresso the medium roast beans would produce. Firing up the espresso maker I was impressed by the crema that it produced. Its hard to explain, but the espresso looked like a miniature Guinness being poured as the golden hue of the crema rose to the top. I did not find the espresso to be bitter or harsh, its very smooth without sacrificing complex tastes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Illy Fine Grind Espresso Coffee (Regular &amp;amp; Decaffeinated)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fine grind espresso coffee is suitable for use in espresso. French Press and automatic drip coffee makers. Those using it in an automatic drip coffee maker may find that the coffee is thicker than you are normally used to due to the fineness of the grind. If you find this to be a problem, consider using a finer mesh gold coffee filter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Burnt Taste &amp;amp; Bite Missing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In testing the Illy coffee I included a number of different people in the testing process. After all, coffee is better enjoyed with friends! People immediately noticed the the Illy coffee lacks the burnt overcooked taste all too common in other coffees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It lacks a harsh aftertaste which allows the coffee to finish strong without being overpowering. I really felt like I could enjoy and explore the complexity of tastes that the Illy blend of coffee brings to the table. I am very curious to try the Illy dark roast coffee and compare it to the medium roast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is an important point to consider. If you try a coffee, and feel intrigued and excited to try the offer roasts or blends that they offer, the coffee is a success in my opinion. The great thing about coffee is that it is something we can all afford, I would encourage you to try Illy if you have the chance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Illy coffee can be ordered online at the Illy Shop. We would like to thank Bratskeir &amp;amp; Company for the opportunity to review this coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/17/Illy-Medium-Roast-Espresso-Coffee.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/17/Illy-Medium-Roast-Espresso-Coffee.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Door County Caffeine Distributors</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While the family and I rushed out of the house for a three day weekend in Door County Wisconsin, we forgot something important.  Not our kids, or toothbrushes, but our coffee maker.  Normally I wouldn’t even consider bringing a coffee maker, but I’m using the AeroPress, so it’s small and very transportable.  In addition, we’ve become somewhat of coffee snobs, so not just any coffee will do.  Anyway, we were lucky enough to find a couple places to satisfy our coffee needs in Door County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first place we tried was LeRoy’s in Ephraim, Wisconsin, which is on the west side of the peninsula.  LeRoy’s has been around for 14 years and is located right off the main drag in the downtown area.  Now before you get too excited, know that it’s not a coffee house that you would frequent for poetry, lush leather chairs, or other such niceties in some coffee houses.  That said, LeRoy’s offers a good variety of the most popular coffee drinks, brewed to perfection.  In addition to drinks, they offer various pastries of all kinds.  I was happy to find this place and will definitely return when back in Door County.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our other caffeine joint we found was Dewey’s, between Gills Rock and Sister Bay, which is a little more north than Ephraim, near the tip of Door County.  Just like LeRoy’s it’s not really a place to hangout, but does have good coffee.  I had their house blend which is a combination of a light and dark roast from Zimbabwe and Columbia.  They offer other coffee drinks, and have been around for four years.  They get their coffee from a distributor in Milwaukee and had good fresh coffee on hand when I went in.  While they don’t offer sandwiches or a lot of other goodies, Dewey’s wife makes cornbread and chili in the winter for snowmobile season.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either place should satisfy your coffee cravings when in northern Door County, and I recommend them both.  There are other coffee shops in Door County, but drink their coffee at your own risk.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/wisconsin/coffee%20shop/2006/08/12/Door-County-Caffeine-Distributors.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/wisconsin/coffee%20shop/2006/08/12/Door-County-Caffeine-Distributors.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
        <category>wisconsin</category>
        
        <category>coffee shop</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jura-Capresso IMPRESSA E9</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Continuing on with the Jura-Capresso tradition of fine coffee products — the IMPRESSA E9 Super Automatic Coffee Center offers an extensive array of features and functionality sure to satisfy both the die hard espresso aficionado as well as the casual espresso drinker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Normally these two types of people would be hard pressed to find a single machine capable of satisfying both of their needs. Let’s be honest, some of the best espresso makers are also some of the most frightening looking contraptions in the coffee world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And while the sight of a pump action espresso machine with its multitude of gauges and dials may make many a coffee aficionados’ eyes glitter in appreciation, most casual espresso drinkers would run screaming for the hills (or at least Starbucks).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IMPRESSA E9 is classed as an “Super Automatic Coffee Center”. Aside from filling the unit with water and coffee beans, all other operations are automated via the push of a button or turn of a knob.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the things that impresses me about the E9 is it sleek and classical look. Some coffee makers depend on electronic flash to attract attention. With the IMPRESSA E9 the controls and display are kept to a minimum, anything more would distract from the aesthetic appreciation of this unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Left side of the E9 houses the water tank (holds enough water for 40 cups of espresso, less if you use the steamer). A flip up lid on the top of the E9 allows the water tank to be lifted out by its built in handle. The E9 features a CLEARYL Water Care System. This system removes chlorine, lead, aluminum and copper. In addition the CLEARYL system contains a special organic additive that removes the vast majority of carbon and eliminates decalcifying altogether.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A matching flip up lid on the right side of the E9 gives access to the coffee bean reservoir and burr grinder. The burr grinder has four grind settings that can set for use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Powering on the E9 initiates a startup cycle that preps the system and begins heating water. The display on the E9 indicates a status of “HEATING” which is replaced by the word “RINSE” after around 30 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressing the “RINSE” button will cycle a small amount of water through the E9 and out the twin coffee spout. Don’t worry about having a cup to catch the water, it flows easily out and through slots in the chrome base for this purpose. Once completed, the display will read — “READY” at which point espresso can be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the things that surprised me was just how much feedback the E9 gives during its operation. For instance, when the supply of beans becomes low, it tell you to — “FILL BEANS”. When the water supply is low, it tell you to “FILL WATER”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make too many espressos without emptying the internal ground collector and it will tell you to “EMPTY GROUNDS”, consequently the E9 will tell you that the “DRAWER MISSING” when you pull out the drawer to empty the grounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What is the point of having an “Automatic Coffee Center” if you have to constantly stop to check if you need to do maintenance or refills?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The E9 allows you to focus on making espresso and steaming milk rather than checking to see if its time to refill the machine or perform maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make an espresso one simply presses the single cup button. The large knob on the left will light up red and display the amount of espresso to be made in ounces or milliliters (default setting is for ounces). Turning the knob will allow you to set the amount of espresso to be made. The initial setting is for four ounces, the maximum single cup size to be made is eight ounces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressing the two cup button will double brew whatever the amount of espresso you have set for the single cup button (16 ounces is the maximum amount of espresso that the two cup button will brew). Regardless of which button you choose, both spouts are utilized in the espresso brewing process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pressing the one or two cup button once will cause the display to read “MILD”, pressing it again will change the strength display to “NORMAL”, pressing it a third time will change the display to read “STRONG” (optionally holding the button down will cause it to cycle through these options).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Espresso brewed with the “MILD” setting will grind beans for 6-7 seconds, “NORMAL” will grind for 7.5 to 8.5 seconds and “STRONG” for 9 to 10 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The E9 has two Aroma settings that directly affect the grinding times (accessible via the setup button). The “STANDARD” aroma setting uses the shorter grinding times, while the “ROBUST” setting will use the longer grinding times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another nice feature that the E9 has is its adjustable coffee spout height. While some people may prefer to use the traditional demitasse cups for their espresso, others may prefer to brew the espresso directly into their coffee cups to avoid any loss of potential crema.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With espresso made, thoughts turn to steaming milk. Pressing the button that looks like a nozzle with steam coming out will begin the steam heating process. The same control knob used to set the espresso volume will again be backlit red and the display will show the last steam time setting set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The E9 can be set to output between 3 and 120 seconds of steam. Steam is heated very quickly in the E9 — 15 to 30 seconds. When ready the display will say “STEAM READY”, at which point the knob on the top right hand side of thee E9 can be turned to the steam position. When the E9 has output your desired amount of steam it will ask you to “SHUT TAP”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steam burns can be quite serious, please keep this in mind when using the E9 steaming functions. A significant amount of steam pressure is generated by the E9. Make sure you have the nozzle in milk, or wrapped in a wet towel if cleaning to minimize the possibility of getting a burn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also want to point out the the steam nozzle attachment can be removed for cleaning or replacement. Make sure that it is securely attached to the unit before you turn the steam into the on position. Avoid turning on the steam if the nozzle is not fully installed on the unit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have an urge to use decaffeinated or pre-ground flavored coffee, there is a special button on the front of the unit that looks like a coffee scoop. When pressed the E9 will tell you to “FILL POWDER”. Open the lid on the top middle of the unit and fill the funnel with one or two scoops of ground coffee (Do not use more than two scoops of coffee, and never use instant coffee unless you want to void your warranty and be the object of ridicule for even thinking of using instant coffee).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As much as I like espresso, I do get a craving for my French press from time to time. The E9 can put hot water easily within my reach. By simply turning the steam nob from the coffee position the to steam position, hot water will be run through the steam attachment. The amount of hot water dispensed can be set from 1 to 16 ounces via the setting knob on the left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The E9 allows customization of the Auto Shut-Off time, this can be set from zero (never shuts off) to nine hours. When the unit shuts down automatically it will perform a rinse cycle similar to the one done during a cold start of the system (this can be turned off if so desired in the setup menus).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Believe it or not, the E9 actually keeps usage statistics! Not only can it tell you how many total cups of espresso you have brewed, pressing the 1-Cup, 2-Cup and Ground coffee button will display statistics for each of those buttons used.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;During our Review Process we Enjoyed…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;91 Total Cups of Espresso&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;89 of which were 1-Cup Draws (4 Oz.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;02 of which were 2-Cup Draws (8 Oz.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;00 of which were Pre-Ground&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A multitude of languages can be set for use on the E9 — English, German, French, Italian, Spanish, Portuguese and Dutch (NL) can all be chose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After around 200 coffees the manual indicates that the the unit will tell you it is time to clean the machine, in addition it will tell you when it is time to perform a decalcification of the machine should it be needed. Both procedures are well documented, and can be reviewed in further detail online at Capresso should you be interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;So what does it cost?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Priced from $999.00 to $1,199.00 the IMPRESSA E9 has a higher price point than many espresso makers, but keep in mind that trying to compare this machine to anything you will find in a home or department store is like trying to compare coach to first class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The IMPRESSA E9 is an amazing machine and investment if you want to appreciate great espresso and consistent crema without the hassles that more manual systems face. Even my wife (who would normally avoid an espresso machine like the plague) has fallen under the spell of this unit. I think she has been to Starbucks once since receiving this unit for review, and even then she complained that the latte she had earlier at home was better than what she got at Starbucks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That being said I would buy this unit in a heartbeat if we were not saving every penny for our upcoming adoption from China, somethings I must admit are more important than even the finest espresso machine. Such is life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with my prior Capresso review I would like to thank the fine people at Field &amp;amp; Associates for giving me the opportunity to review this fine product.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/07/Jura-Capresso-IMPRESSA-E9.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/07/Jura-Capresso-IMPRESSA-E9.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Seattle Chocolates Espresso Truffles</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If its hot and humid enough, even the staunchest coffee drinker will look for alternative ways to enjoy coffee. This weekend some friends provided such an outlet for my coffee cravings - Espresso Truffles.  This being my first experience with the Seattle Chocolates Company, I was not sure what to expect. If the presentation was any indication of the chocolate inside (the ribbon is nice touch), I was in for a treat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opening the box revealed individually wrapped candy, I quickly opened one of the truffles and found something I love — Dark Chocolate. Things were starting to look promising!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now there are two types of candy eaters in my opinion, those who take several bites to extend the enjoyment time of the candy, and those who take more of a neanderthalian approach and pop the entire treat into their mouth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since it was an espresso truffle I threw decorum out the window and popped the entire piece in my mouth. As my teeth breached the dark chocolate exterior I quickly discovered the espresso infused milk chocolate interior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unlike lesser creations that simple add coffee flavouring to their chocolate, these truffles contain actual espresso coffee. The espresso flavour is clearly evident along with hints of vanilla and coconut. I could eat an entire box of these truffles they are that good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought I quite possibly had found the perfect melding of chocolate and coffee until to my horror I read on the ingredient list…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Decaffeinated Espresso Coffee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who am I kidding, its hard to split hairs about something like this when you are talking about fine chocolate. I will be buying these for my coffee loving friends soon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/01/Seattle-Chocolates-Espresso-Truffles.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/08/01/Seattle-Chocolates-Espresso-Truffles.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bialetti Mukka Express</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/half-banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Mukka, Mukka, Mukka! I don’t know if it was it’s quirky design (cow print), the promise of the perfect stove top cappuccino, or the unknown mysteries of the Moka pot that had me giddy with anticipation to try the Bialetti Mukka Express.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I waited for my Mukka Express to be delivered I stumbled across a fantastic article by Myron Joshua called “The Story of the Bialetti Moka Express” on www.ineedcoffee.com. In this article Myron speaks in depth about the history of Bialetti and his Moka vision. Bialetti promised:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Espresso in the Home Just Like in the Bar”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bialetti Mukka Express is an updated version of their traditional Moka pot. The Mukka Express has a number of other finish options available if the cow print does not suit your tastes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Central to the unit is a two position value that allows one to toggle between cappuccino mode, and “milk coffee” mode (aka latte). Depressing the value sets the Mukka Express to cappuccino mode, keeping it in the up position sets it to latte mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you can see the Mukka Express is made up of two sections. The bottom basin holds the water and percolator basket. The upper pot screws onto this and is where the milk is added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The then combined unit is placed on the stove and when the pressure in the basin reaches its crescendo, the upper value pops, causing the coffee to forcefully combine with the milk. Steam moving from the bottom chamber into the top causes the milk to foam. The end result being a perfect cappuccino.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;According to the Video…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In reality, obtaining those results is not as easy as it is portrayed. During the initial break in period Bialetti suggests that three pots be made and discarded without milk. No problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I carefully filled the bottom with the exact amount of water indicated. Added my grounds to the percolator basket making sure to not pack the coffee or get it on the surrounding threads. And set my flame to medium as requested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About five minutes later I heard the pop of the value being tripped, and excitedly watched to see what would happen. Coffee began to rush into the upper pot, it tumultuously rolled and thrashed as the steam forced its way up into the pot, up, up and over it boiled..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;All over my freshly cleaned stove.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife eyed the Mukka Express with a slightly less enthused look, I could tell she was beginning to question its “cute” factor. Not a problem I assured here, the heat may have been too high, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Attempt number two was made…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Honey I am going to need some more towels..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By attempt three I decided to throw caution to the wind, and dare I say it, add milk to the top. When the valve popped I opened the lid and yes, the milk was countering the explosive nature of the coffee, but it too continued to rise up and ultimately… overflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time thankfully, I had more or less spared the stove. The instructional video on the Bialetti site shows the Mukka Express filling two giant cappuccino cups, in reality it just barely filled two regular coffee cups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a number of additional trials with different beans, grind consistencies and water and milk volumes (it seems using slightly more water and milk that they suggest is needed to avoid the boil over effect when using 2% milk, skim may be different), I was able to get the Mukka Express to bubble to rim of the pot just like the video shows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are not willing to go through a trial and error period like this, you might want to consider a coffee brewing method that will give you more uniform results. Also, I would like to point out that moka brewed coffee has a unique, earthy almost industrial taste to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have never had this type of coffee before, try some first before you buy a moka pot to make sure you like it. At around $90 the Mukka Express will not break the bank, but I would hate to see someone buy one expecting it to taste like something other than what it does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I really like the idea of doing everything in one pot, I can see the merits of keeping the two processes separate. Your control is limited with the Mukka Express. Again this can either be a good or bad thing depending on the type of coffee drinker you are.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2006 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/07/29/Bialetti-Mukka-Express.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://reviewmonkey.org/coffee/2006/07/29/Bialetti-Mukka-Express.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>coffee</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
