<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Monkey See, Monkey Do, Monkey Review</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 16:26:14 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 16:26:14 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Into the Spiderverse</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wow, what can I say other than this movie is a pure treat to watch. As a long time Spiderman fan, someone who grew up in the 1970’s watching the original Spiderman cartoon, watching the terrible live action Spiderman movies that were on TV, and all of the various later renditions with Toby and others, you would think I would have been first in line for this animated movie?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I almost didn’t go. Don’t get me wrong, he is still one of my favorite superheros, but after all of the earlier renditions, a person starts to wonder if the latest movie will actually bring something to the table or if it will just be another cookie cutter repeat. At $9+ bucks a ticket these days, that is a valid question to ask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I knew I would have some free time today, and I knew my son wanted to go see it (17) and figured he would go want to go with his friends as boys that age tend to want to do, but he was up for going to see it with his old man, so we went.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Spoilers Will be Revealed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just want to put that out there, I’m not going to talk about the plot, give you a run down minute by minute. I went into this movie knowing it was animated and that there was going to be Nicholas Cage in it and that there was going to be more that one Spiderman. That was about it, and I have to say I am glad I didn’t know more, not because it would have ruined the movie, but I like coming into a movie fresh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;amazing-visual-style&quot;&gt;Amazing Visual Style&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an animated feature film, I could tell from the opening credits and score that this movie was going to be different. The visual styles were fresh, explosive even, the audio assails you in a good way, and the way they characters were rendered gave you the feeling of a comic book but also a more traditional anime movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This continues throughout the movie and made this feel like something completely new. Even the various villains and supporting characters take on new twists and subtle changes in a way that makes them feel completely new and exciting. The experience that I expected to be mildly entertained had me on my seat during many parts of the movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;great-story&quot;&gt;Great Story&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As amazing as the visuals and sound were, a movie with a poor excuse of a story will not stand the test of time. Granted this is a superhero movie and isn’t ever going to be a Casablanca or Gone With the Wind, I am going to going to say that it is the best Spiderman movie to date, with Spiderman: Homecoming a close second. And while a lot of movies are as good at home as they are in the theater, I definitely recommend that you go see this in the theater where you can get the full audio and visual impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;nicholas-cage&quot;&gt;Nicholas Cage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last thing I am going to say, Nicholas Cage did a fantastic job. He often gets a bad wrap for his acting (sometimes for good reason), but I’ve been a fan since Raising Arizona and I thought he did a great job voice acting in this movie.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all I have for now, thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/movie/spiderman/marvel/sony/2018/12/15/Into_the_SpiderVerse.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/movie/spiderman/marvel/sony/2018/12/15/Into_the_SpiderVerse.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>spiderman</category>
        
        <category>marvel</category>
        
        <category>sony</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Otterbox Commuter</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/half-banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Otterbox has long been known for their battle hardened cases that iPhone and Android users have flocked to over the years to protect and cradle the special child that will take up some much of their time and attention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They make cases that are designed to protect the baby phone if it is dropped, encase it in a protective sleeve, and in the case of the Defender line a protective plastic face. They are for all practical purposes armor for your phone and I can attest that my son’s Defender case kept his iPhone safe through the harsh junior high years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But this review isn’t about the Defender case, it is about it’s little brother – The Commuter series case. I would describe the commuter case as a case for the slightly paranoid user who occasionally drops his or her phone. It takes the features found in the Defender series and shaves them down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me explain.  With the Defender case the user puts the phone into a plastic shell that has a plastic cover and snaps it together. Think Vader getting his helmet. A rubber sleeve is then put around the case. With the Commuter series case this gets reversed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a thick rubber sleeve that goes around the back and sides of phone leaving the front glass exposed. A hard plastic shell that grips the phone on the top, bottom and sides with some convenient cutouts to reduce the hard plastic surface area and expose some of the underlying rubber. The result is a much less boxy case that minimally adds to the bulk.  The attached runner ports keep the lightning port and the headphone jack (how quaint, a headphone jack) covered until needed.  The sound off and on switch oddly does not have a port cover.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-i-came-to-the-case&quot;&gt;How I Came to the Case&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I first bought my iPhone 6 Plus I decided to go the Apple Leather Case route. I was older, more refined, careful.  It seemed perfect. And for a long time it was. I had maybe a single minor drop of a foot with no issue, and generally babied the hell out of the phone, but I would put it in my front pocket. And over time the flex the phone received from sitting down, getting in the car, etc. was enough to cause one of the internal boards to start having a short, and my touchscreen would flicker and stop working.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By some stroke of luck Apple care actually replaced the phone for a new one, but the sleek leather case wasn’t going to cut it.  I needed this phone to last years.  But I didn’t want to go for the full Defender case. Here was a sleek phone, did I really want to encase it in a block? As I mentioned I have done it in the past, but this time I decided to make a compromise and went for the Otterbox Commuter series.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;overall-impression&quot;&gt;Overall Impression&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t say that there is anything I dislike about this case. The hard outer shell that snaps around the rubber sleeve does a good job of protecting the phone from drops. I have dropped my phone with this case easily twenty or thirty times from various heights. The phone is still working without fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only casualty as can be seen in the picture is the lower corner on one side that took the hit it was intended to do and broke. I can only guess that it was one of the harder falls and maybe hit something just right. The loss of plastic hasn’t hindered the case, but it’s an area that now has slightly less protection, so I’ll have to just hope the rubber does the trick in that area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had this case for more than four years now and it has held up remarkably well. These phones cost so much these days, its only natural to want to put the most protection around the phone that you can, nobody wants to see $800-$1000 just go poof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Otterbox commuter satisfies that need in my opinion.  It has given me peace of mind while still letting me enjoy the slim nature of the phone. Thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/iphone/case/2018/12/13/otterbox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/iphone/case/2018/12/13/otterbox.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>iphone</category>
        
        <category>case</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Surface Book</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bananas:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/banana.png&quot; alt=&quot;banana&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Microsoft Surface Book was released to the world on October 26, 2015 according to Wikipedia. It featured a two-in-one tablet design that people who liked the Surface tabled line but wanted a traditional laptop could get behind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I purchased my Surface Book sometime in 2016 at the suggestion of a friend who was in love with his. There was a lot to like about it, it was sleek, felt well made, had a funky bendy hinge that people on the net were either loving or hating, and once a special came up on the Microsoft store, I decided to take the plunge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now there are tons of reviews out there that tech fetish spew out the specs, I am not going to do that. Let’s face it, this is an older laptop and this review is really meant for the people looking for a laptop on the cheap. So I will be focusing on what I like and don’t like about this laptop after living with it for 2+ years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;general-impressions--internet-woes&quot;&gt;General Impressions / Internet Woes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned earlier, the build quality on this laptop is really pretty fantastic. Every edge has a finished feel, there is no flex or pieces that are pulling apart even after 2 years. The hinge which at the time I bought it was being depicted as something of a joke hasn’t shown any signs of failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large number of people at the time made it out to be wobbly, and if you were to having it on your lap and type it would slightly jiggle. I’ve used this a number of times on my lap and that has never been an issue. If it was I didn’t notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I recall there were also some people that were running into issues with heat from the base of the units that included the build in GPU (which I bought) causing damage to the screen near the vents. This is something that I &lt;strong&gt;could&lt;/strong&gt; see happening if one were to play a GPU intensive game for long periods, it does get pretty warm and I can imagine people sitting in a Starbucks doing just that, closing it up and putting it into a backpack where the screen would have a nice chance to bake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never decided to test that theory, at times when I was playing GPU intensive games I would always just shut it down and leave it open, letting it cool down before closing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gaming&quot;&gt;Gaming&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me just say that gaming on this Surface Book with the weak sauce GPU it has (I do not have the performance based) is sub-par at best. I’ve played some Borderlands on it, some Elder Scrolls Online, even a bit of Fortnite and it has just been ok (with significant toning down of effects). In a pinch it works, but if you can stick to less intensive games you will be better off.  But really, &lt;strong&gt;seriously&lt;/strong&gt; if playing games is a primary focus for you, do not buy this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;linux&quot;&gt;Linux&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been dual booting this Surface Book pretty much since I bought it. I am using Ubuntu Mate at the moment but most distros should work just fine provided that you get the Jakeday kernel. It doesn’t support the GPU and the built in cameras are not working yet, but touch seems to work fairly well.  His repo is &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jakeday/linux-surface&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-annoys-me&quot;&gt;What Annoys Me&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to say that the HDPI 3000x2000 screen turned out to be something I have not been the biggest fan of. What I didn’t realize, or maybe I just convinced myself that it wouldn’t be an issue, is that many applications do not play nicely with HDPI screens. Applications will open with tiny interfaces, or the interface will scale incorrectly, or the menus will be all bonkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using a Linux distro that supports HDPI is key, and for the most part it does a better job than Windows but just marginally. Some apps are fine and maybe its just applications I am playing with where the developer didn’t stop to build in support for HDPI that are the issue. On the Windows side the occasional application runs into the same issue. The Windows application override for scaling can sometimes do the trick, but more often than not it just makes things absolutely tiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running at a lower resolution is an option, but the Surface Book really looks its best in its native 3000x2000 resolution. In both Windows and Linux I have had to either put it in HDPI mode to have the system scale the UI or in Windows increase the text scaling. This is likely because I am old, young whipper snappers might be just fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For games the oddball resolutions that this supports for the game to be in the proper aspect ratio are often not supported by the game and one needs to add them into config files, etc.  This is something else to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving My Face Close to the Screen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way too often I find myself taking my glasses off and putting my nose 3-5 inches away from the screen. This always happens when my wife is in close proximity so she can say “That can’t be good for your eyes”. And I agree, there is just something about this HDPI screen that my eyes don’t like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can safely say that my next laptop will not have a HDPI screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-drives-me-insane&quot;&gt;What Drives Me Insane&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, here is the part of the review you should really take note and pay attention to because this issue drives me bonkers.  Much has been said about how much the touchpad is like the holy grail touchpad found on Apple laptops, and as a touchpad, I have no complaints.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what this touchpad does that the Apple touchpads does not do it decide to go rogue and move your cursor around the screen when you type. I can’t tell you how many times I have been typing on the built in keyboard in Word or another application only to find my cursor jumping up or down or over to another position while I am typing and royally messing things up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only solution I have found for this is to either a) use an external keyboard (lol it just skipped around as I was writing this using the built in keyboard - Arrggh!) which isn’t a bad idea when you are at the home office, but the point is to be mobile.  Or b) when using Windows, there is an option to disable the touchpad when an external mouse is plugged in, using a Bluetooth mouse, no luck, you need a wired mouse, which is janky as hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Microsoft has had a number of updated for the Surface Book to fix a number of major issues but this issue continues to persist which makes me think that there is no solution for it an it is likely a physical issue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tablet-mode&quot;&gt;Tablet Mode&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly I have not found myself using it in tablet mode. It gives you a full page landscape or portrait viewing experience which is pretty nice. And the way that the tablet detaches from the base will delight Star Trek fans who got giddy whenever the Enterprise would detach the saucer section, but the batter life isn’t as good as what a dedicated Surface or Ipad would give. You can always turn it around and use it with the base in tablet mode but it is a bit bulky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both of these are not deal killers to me, and maybe I just need to spend more time using it as a tablet to see if it makes me forget about the touchpad and keyboard. But probably not, that really fucking annoys me when it jumps around).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So there you have it, this monkey’s honest review of the original Surface Book.  I am going to give it three bananas because of the annoyance the keyboard and trackpad gives me on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>/laptop/tech/tablet/2018/12/12/surfacebook.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/laptop/tech/tablet/2018/12/12/surfacebook.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>laptop</category>
        
        <category>tech</category>
        
        <category>tablet</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
